{
  "0": {
    "prompt": "Dota Hero by quote: I am the dead of winter!",
    "answer": "Lich"
  },
  "1": {
    "prompt": "Dota Hero by quote: Ah these mortals and their futile games. Oh wait! I'm one of them! Hah ha ha ha ha!",
    "answer": "Zeus"
  },
  "2": {
    "prompt": "Dota Hero by quote: You know I'm really not a fan of that dying thing. No, it's not for me.",
    "answer": "Timbersaw"
  },
  "3": {
    "prompt": "Dota Hero by quote: What is Luke's real mmr?",
    "answer": ":lcurley:"
  },
  "4": {
    "prompt": "Dota Hero by quote: Just have a seat right over there. And let the smart people work.",
    "answer": "Techies"
  },
  "5": {
    "prompt": "Dota Hero by quote: Do you know why they call it the Nether Reaches? Because it reaches into you.",
    "answer": "Pugna"
  },
  "6": {
    "prompt": "Dota Hero by quote: When the whirling one rains death upon your head, no bunker can protect you.",
    "answer": "Oracle"
  },
  "7": {
    "prompt": "Dota Hero by quote: I had a vision of this place in the Temple of Mene, but I had no idea it was a prophecy.",
    "answer": "Mirana"
  },
  "8": {
    "prompt": "Dota Hero by quote: I thought I hated demons, but I didn't know what hate was till I met that Shadow Fiend.",
    "answer": "Kunkka"
  },
  "9": {
    "prompt": "Notable People: Which slumlord turned off the dota 1 forums and redirected it to league?",
    "answer": "Pendrake"
  }
}
